<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="Jaawartou_Ar">
        <item>بِسْمِ اللهِ الرَّحْمَنِ الرَّحِيمِ فَارَقْتُ إِبْلِيسَ وَجَمِيعَ الْمَفَاسِدِ وَبِسْمِ اللهِ الرَّحْمَنِ الرَّحِيمِ لاَزَمْتُ رَسُولَ اللهِ صَلَّى اللهُ تَعَالَى عَلَيْهِ وَسَلَّمَ وَجَمِيعَ الْمَصَالِحِ وَلاَ حَوْلَ وَلاَ قُوَّةَ إِلاَّ بِاللهِ الْعَلِيِّ الْعَظِيمِ</item>
        <item>جَاوَرْتُ اللهَ بِكِتَابِهِ إِلَى دُخُولِيَ جَنَّتَهُ</item>
        <item>جَاوَرْتُ بِالْفُرْقَانِ رَبِّيَ الْمُعِينْ      مَلَكْتُ نَفْسِيَ وَزَحْزَحْتُ اللَّعِينَ</item>
        <item>أَخَذْتُ مِنْ دُنْيَاهُ زَادِي لِلْجِنَانْ      وَانْقَادَ لِي الْهَوَى وَلِيَ صَفَا الْجَنَان</item>
        <item>وَالاَنِيَ اْلاَبْرَارُ فِي أُخْرَايَا      وَانْقَادَ لِي بِلاَ انْتِهًا قِرَايَا</item>
        <item>رَافَقَنِي إِلَى الْجِنَانِ جِيمُ      وَلِسِوَايَ زُحْزِحَ الرَّجِيمُ</item>
        <item>تُرْسِي عَنِ اللَّعِينِ وَالْفُجَّارِ      كَوْنُ بَدِيعِ الْعَالَمِينَ جَارِي</item>
        <item>أَكْرَمَنِي الْبَدِيعُ بِالْكِتَابِ      وَصَانَنِي عَنْ جَالِبِ الْعِتَابِ</item>
        <item>لَمْ يَنْحُنِي إِلَى دُخُولِي الْجَنَهْ      غَيْرُ بُشَارَاتِ العَلِي ذِي الْمِنَهْ</item>
        <item>لَمْ يَنْحُنِي زَجْرٌ وَلاَ وَعِيدُ      وَعُمُرِي إِلَى الْجِنَانِ عِيدُ</item>
        <item>أَخْفَى لِيَ السِّرَ الْمَصُونَ اللهُ      حُبًّا وَلاَ إِلَهَ إِلاَّ اللهُ</item>
        <item>هَدَانِيَ اللهُ وَإِنَّهُ الْبَدِيعْ      وَقَادَنِي لَهُ بِأَنْوَاعِ الْبَدِيعْ</item>
        <item>بَرَّأَنِي الْخَالِقُ مِنْ سِوَاهُ      وَقَادَنِي مَنْ لاَ يُرَى شَرْوَاهُ</item>
        <item>كِتَابُ رَبِّي كَانَ لِي وَكُنْتُ      لَهُ وَللهِ بِهِ سَكَنْتُ</item>
        <item>تُرْسِي عَنِ اْلأَكْدَارِ وَالْمَفَاسِدِ      سَلاَمَتِي مِنْ جَالِبٍ لِفَاسِدِ</item>
        <item>أَكْرَمَنِي اللهُ بِذِكْرِهِ وَمَا      لِي اخْتَارَهُ وَلِيَ قَادَ اْلأَقْوَمَا</item>
        <item>بَاهَى بِيَ اللهُ الْكِرَامَ الْغُرَّا      وَبِبَقَائِيَ النَّبِيَّ سَرَّا</item>
        <item>هِبَاتُ ذِي الْجَلاَلِ وَاْلإِكْرَامِ      لِي خَلَّدَتْ مُرَغِّبَ الْكِرَامِ</item>
        <item>إِلَيَّ قَادَ اللهُ مَا لَمْ يَكُنِ      وَلاَ يَكُونُ أَبَدًا لِلْمُمْكِنِ</item>
        <item>لَسْتُ أَشُكُّ أَبَدًا فِي كَوْنِي      جَارَ الْبَدِيعِ عَجَبًا لِلْكَوْنِ</item>
        <item>إِنَّ الَّذِي مِنَ اْلإِلَهِ حُزْتُ      غَابَ عَنِ الْكَوْنِ وَفِيهِ فُزْتُ</item>
        <item>دَلَّنِيَ اللهُ عَلَى اللهِ بِلاَ      تَغَرُّرٍ وَعُمُرِي تَقَبَّلاَ</item>
        <item>خَابَتْ قُلاَتِيَ مَعَ الْحُسَّادِ      مُذْ ثَمَنِي حُزْتُ بِلاَ كَسَاد</item>
        <item>وَقَانِيَ الْبَاقِي بِهِ ثَبُورَا      تِجَارَتِي لَدَيْهِ لَنْ تَبُورَا</item>
        <item>لَمْ يَنْحُنِي مَا بَاعَ عَنِّي اللهُ      فَضْلاً وَلاَ إِلَهَ إِلاَّ اللهُ</item>
        <item>يَقُودُ لِي بِلاَ انْتِهَاءٍ ثَمَنِي      مَنْ كَانَ لِي وَلِيَ صَفَّى زَمَنِي</item>
        <item>جَاوَرْتُ رَبِّي بِلِسَانِ الْعَرَبِ      بِلاَ نِهَايَةٍ وَتَابَتْ قُرَبِ</item>
        <item>نَزَعَ لِي اْلإِسْلاَمَ عِنْدَ غُرْبَتِي      لَدَى الْجَزَائِرِ مُنِيرُ تُرْبَتِي</item>
        <item>نُزِعَ لِي نُورُ اللِّسَانِ وَالْكِتَابْ      أَزْمَانَ خِدْمَتِي لَدَى أَهْلِ الْكِتَابْ</item>
        <item>تَذْيِيلُ مَا ثَبَتَ لِلْمُشَفَّعِ      أَغْنَى يَمِينِي عَنْ أَذًى وَمِدْفَعِ</item>
        <item>هَدَانِيَ اللهُ وَزَحْزَحَ اللَّعِينْ      إِلَى سِوَى عُمْرِيَ حَبَّذَا الْمُعِينْ</item>
        <item>سبُحْاَنَ رَبِّكَ رَبِّ الْعِزَّةِ وَسَلاَمٌ عَلَى الْمُرْسَلِينَ وَالْحَمْدُ للهِ رَبِّ الْعَالَمِينَ</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Jaawartou_Fr">
        <item>"I got rid of Satan the devil and all bad deeds or criminal acts thanks to the advantages and benefits of the "basmala" and the "hawqala" I m linked to the prophet and the chosen ones"</item>
        <item>"Admittedly I reside from now on with God, by His holy Book and this until I enter his paradise."</item>
        <item>"Thanks to the Quran, I live with my Lord, the Incomparable Auxiliary, I gained full control of my soul and expelled Satan, the outcast."</item>
        <item>"In this world, I just take my sacrament only for Paradise and I conquered my passion and my heart completely purified."</item>
        <item>"In the Hereafter, the Righteous will be my companions and I will forever be given the means to fulfill."</item>
        <item>"The Qur'an will remain my true companion up to the third Heavens as he drove away from me, Satan, the Stoned."</item>
        <item>"My Shield against the curse and the wicked is the fact that I live with the Creator of the Worlds."</item>
        <item>"The Innovator, through His Book, honors and preserves me from any source of Reprimand."</item>
        <item>"So I would do know, until I went to Paradise, that Joy provided by the Sublime, Benefactor."</item>
        <item>"Would I, nor, subject to any sort of threat or Remonstrance, and my existence will be up to Paradise, Permanent Celebration."</item>
        <item>"GOD conceal the mystery for me, Well Kept (Sirru-l-Mas'un) by Love and by the phrase "Laa ilaaha Laah illa" (There is no other god but God)."</item>
        <item>"GOD directed me [on His Path] - While it remains the Innovative! - and He led me to Him through all sorts of Wonders."</item>
        <item>"The Creator, THE SAME which no one has seen the pair, made me free from everything that is not Him and led me [on the Straight Way]."</item>
        <item>"While the Book of my Lord is in my favor and there is no doubt that I will remain forever in its service because it was through it that I live with GOD."</item>
        <item>"My strict abstinence from any source of corruption is my Bulwark against contamination and harm."</item>
        <item>"While God has honored me by His Book by building and by what He has deigned chosen in me, and to me He has drained the crowds."</item>
        <item>"My Shield against the curse and the wicked is the fact that I live with the Creator of the Worlds."</item>
        <item>"The miracles of the Holder of Majesty and Nobility have never perpetuated my noble ambitions."</item>
        <item>"*God has granted me that, ever, was and will never be granted to any creature.*"</item>
        <item>"In any circumstance have I doubt my capacity to live with the Innovative - that His creation is Wonderful!"</item>
        <item>"The Favors I obtained from GOD exist anywhere in the universe, and this is where my success is."</item>
        <item>"GOD HIMSELF Led me to GOD, with no illusions, and has approved all my life."</item>
        <item>"My enemies and the envious were all disappointed in their expectations while I Award the recipient of my service without any kind of bankruptcy."</item>
        <item>"Thanks to the Koran, God, The Remaining, preserved me against all ruin and my transaction with HIM will never slump of."</item>
        <item>"By His Grace and Infinite by the phrase "Laa ilaaha illa Laah" God will never allow my soul deviate far from my person."</item>
        <item>"God, he who remains in my favor, I paid the salary [of my service to the Prophet], and my person has purified our age."</item>
        <item>"I will dwell forever with my Lord through the [Holy Book written] in Arabic and is excellent with me near HIM."</item>
        <item>"God, he who has enlightened my soul, has entrusted me Islam in deposit during my exile in the islands."</item>
        <item>"It has continued to flood my being the Light of Arabic and the Holy Book every time during my Service to the Prophet among the people of the Book (the colonists)."</item>
        <item>"The Revelation of Truth Intangible (the Quran) to Muhammad, the Intercessor Dealer, is enough for me as a shield against damage and the guns."</item>
        <item>"GOD Directed and has chased out of my life Satan, the Forsaken; How AUXILIARY Excellent!"</item>
        <item>"Praise to God, God of power, grants Your Salvation to the messengers! Glory to God, Lord of the worlds."</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Jaawartou_Tr">
        <item>"Bismil Lahir Rahmanir Rahimi, Fâraqtu Iblîssa wa jamî 'al mafâssidi  wa bismil lahir rahmanir rahimi, laâzamtou rassulal lâhi sallal lâhu 'alayhi wassallama, wa jamî'al massâlihi walâ hawla walâ qouwata illâ billahil 'alliyil azîmi"</item>
        <item>"Jaawartul lâha bikitabihî ila dukhûliya jannatahû"</item>
        <item>"Jâwartu bil   furqâni  rabbiyal   mou ‘ine Malaktu  nafsiya  wa  zahzahtu  la’ine"</item>
        <item>"Akhaztu min dunyâhu zâdî lil-jinâne Wan-qâda  lil  hawâ   walî safal  janâne"</item>
        <item>"Wâ  lâniyal  abrâru  fî  ukhrâyâ Wan qâda lî bilan tihane qirâyâ"</item>
        <item>"Râfaqanî  ilal  jinâni   jîmu Wali siwâya  zuhzihar - rajîmu"</item>
        <item>"Tursî ‘anil la’îni wal fujjâri  Kawnu badî’il ‘âlamîna jâri"</item>
        <item>"Akramanil  badî ‘u  bil  kitâbi Wa  Sânanî  ‘an  jâlibil ‘itâbi"</item>
        <item>"Lame yanhunî ilâ dukhûlil jannah Ghayru buchârâtil ‘alî zil minnah"</item>
        <item>"Lam yanhunî zajrune walâ wa ‘îdu Wa  ‘umurî  ilal jinâni ‘îdu"</item>
        <item>"Akhfâ liyassiral  masunal lâhu  Hubbane  wa  lâ ilâha illal lâhu "</item>
        <item>"Hadâniyal-lâhu wa innahûl-badîh Wa qâdanî lahû bi anwahil  badih "</item>
        <item>"Barra  anil  khâliqou   mine  siwâhu  Wa qâdanî man lâ yurâ charwâhu "</item>
        <item>"Kitâbu rabbî kâna lî wa kuntu  Lahû wa  lillâhi  bihî sakantu"</item>
        <item>"Tursî ‘anil akdâri wal-mafâsidi Salâmatî min jâlibin lifâsidi"</item>
        <item>"Akramanil  lâhu  bizikrihî  wamâ Likh târahû wa liya qâdal aqwamâ"</item>
        <item>"Bâhâ biya-lâhul-kirâmâl-ghurrâ Wa  bi  baqâ iya nabiyya  sarrâ"</item>
        <item>"Hibâtu  zil  jalâli  wal-ikrâmi Li khalladat muraghabal - kirâmi "</item>
        <item>Ilayya qâdal - Lâhu mâ lam yakuni Walâ  yakûnu  abadane lil  mumkini</item>
        <item>"Lastu achukku abadane fi-kawnî  Jâral-badî’i  hajabane  lil-kawni"</item>
        <item>"Inna-L  lazî  minal  ilâhi  huztu Ghâba ‘anil - kawni wa fîhi fuztu"</item>
        <item>"Dallaniyal  Lâhu  ‘alal-lâhi   bilâ  Tagharrurine wa ‘umurî taqabbalâ"</item>
        <item>"Khâbatt qulâtiya ma’al husadi Mus çamanî  huztou bilâ kasâdi"</item>
        <item>"Waqâniyal baqî bihî çubûrâ  Tijâratî  ladayhi  lane  tabûrâ"</item>
        <item>"Lame yan ‘unî mâ bâ ‘a annil-Lâhu Fadlane  wa lâ  ilâha  illal  Lâhu"</item>
        <item>"Yaqûdu lî bilan tihâ-în çamanî Mane  kana  li wa  lîya  saffâ  zamanî"</item>
        <item>"Jâwartu  Rabbî bi lissâni ‘arabî Bi lâ nihâyatine wa tâbatt qourabî"</item>
        <item>"Naza’a lil- islâma  ‘inda ghurbatî Ladal jazâ’irî  munîru  turbatî"</item>
        <item>"Nuzi’a lî nûrul lisâni wal kitâb Azmâna  khidmatî ladâ  ahlil  kitâb"</item>
        <item>"Tazyîlu ma çabbata lil-muchaffa’I Aghnâ yamîni ‘ane azane  wa midfa’i"</item>
        <item>Hadâniyal  lâhu wa  zahzahal la’îne Ilâ siwâ ‘umriya  habbazal  mu’îne</item>
        <item>"Subhâna Rabbika Rabbil 'izzati 'ammâ yasifûne wa salâmune 'alal mursalîne wal hamdu lil Lâhi Rabbil 'âlamîne"</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="app_name">Jaawartou</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Xamé Thie Serigne Touba</string>
    <string name="songtitle">Xacida Jaawartou</string>
    <string name="app_about">About Jaawartou</string>
    <string name="str_exit">Close</string>
    <string name="str_yes">OK</string>
    <string name="str_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="app_exit_message">Do you to close this application?</string>
    <string name="str_no">No</string>
    <string name="obj1">OUR OBJECTIVE: Working for Cheikh Ahmadou Bamba Khadimou Rassoul for live.</string>
    <string name="obj2">We beseech anyone using this mobile application to pray for SERIGNE SALIOU MBACKE.</string>
    <string name="bienvenu">WELCOME!</string>
    <string name="dieredieuf">DIEUREDIEUF!</string>
    <string name="desc_logo">TAB28</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="timestart">0:00</string>

    <color name="white">#FFFFFF</color>
    <color name="black">#000000</color>

    <string name="title_activity_mon">Jaawartou</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>

</resources>